<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>“The time to relax is when you don\'t have time for it.”
\n– Sydney J. Harris</item>
        <item>“One of the best pieces of advice I ever got was from a horse master. He told me to go slow to go fast. I think that applies to everything in life. We live as though there aren\'t enough hours in the day but if we do each thing calmly and carefully we will get it done quicker and with much less stress.”
\n– Viggo Mortensen</item>
        <item>“Much of the stress that people feel doesn\'t come from having too much to do. It comes from not finishing what they\'ve started.”
\n– David Allen</item>
        <item>“In times of great stress or adversity, it\'s always best to keep busy, to plow your anger and your energy into something positive.”
\n– Lee Iacocca</item>
        <item>“Doing something that is productive is a great way to alleviate emotional stress. Get your mind doing something that is productive.”
\n– Ziggy Marley</item>
        <item>“It is not a daily increase, but a daily decrease. Hack away at the inessentials.”
\n– Bruce Lee</item>
        <item>“The greatest weapon against stress is our ability to choose one thought over another.”
\n– William James</item>
        <item>“We can easily manage if we will only take, each day, the burden appointed to it. But the load will be too heavy for us if we carry yesterday\’s burden over again today, and then add the burden of the morrow before we are required to bear it.”
\n– John Newton</item>
        <item>“It\'s a good idea always to do something relaxing prior to making an important decision in your life.”
\n– Paulo Coelho</item>
        <item>“Take rest; a field that has rested gives a bountiful crop.”
\n– Ovid</item>
        <item>“Stress is caused by being \‘here\' but wanting to be \‘there.\'
\n– Eckhart Tolle</item>
        <item>"The greatest mistake you can make in life is to be continually fearing you will make one."
\n- Elbert Hubbard</item>
        <item>“Its not stress that kills us, it is our reaction to it.”
\n– Hans Selye</item>
        <item>“There are thousands of causes for stress, and one antidote to stress is self-expression. That\'s what happens to me every day. My thoughts get off my chest, down my sleeves and onto my pad.”
\n– Garson Kanin</item>
        <item>“For fast-acting relief, try slowing down.“
\n– Lily Tomlin</item>
        <item>“Somehow our devils are never quite what we expect when we meet them face to face.”
\n– Nelson DeMille</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>